http://www.openbible.org/resources/legal/privacy

Warning! Your browser is extremely outdated and not web standards compliant.Your browsing experience would greatly improve by upgrading to a modern browser.
OpenBible_Logo
Added to your cart:
$0.00
Initial deduction will be made within one business day of donation. Future recurring payments will be deducted on the same date as initial deduction.
ADD ANOTHER DONATION
Checkout
Added to Cart
FindaChurch
Donate
Add to Cart
Total: $0.00
Added to Cart
ResourcesCoronavirus ResponseMessage OnlineOpen Bible ManualInformational MaterialsTraining MaterialsMediaPartnersLegalPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseIn MemoryVision25
Privacy Policy
As Open Bible Churches (OBC), we are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not give, sell, rent or loan any identifiable information regarding visitors to any third party. By using OBC Online, you agree to the Privacy Policy of the Open Bible Churches. The term "OBC Online" refers to the websites under the Open Bible Churches (or "OBC") headquarters, and the department and ministry websites hosted there. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use OBC Online. Open Bible Churches reviews its Privacy Policy periodically and reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. This Privacy Policy applies to all websites produced and maintained by the Open Bible Churches.
If you want to communicate with us regarding our Privacy Policy, please email us, or write us at:
Open Bible Churches
2020 Bell Avenue
Des Moines, IA 50315.
Collection and Use
Open Bible Churches recognizes the privacy concerns of users of OBC Online and the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected from them. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as a visitor's name, address, email address, telephone number, or credit card information is automatically collected on our web site. Such information is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted, and the Open Bible Churches uses such information only for the purpose for which it was submitted, unless we disclose other uses in this policy or at the time of collection. We maintain reasonable and appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of such information in our possession. Open Bible Churches does not sell, trade or rent personally identifiable information to third parties. We reserve the right to monitor traffic patterns and web site usage.
Security
When submitting sensitive data like credit card information, we use 128-bit secure server technology to protect the information. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts the information you input before you send it to us. All of the data is protected against unauthorized access, as indicated by the secure icon on your browser.
Cookies
"Cookies" are files that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information about a user. They enable us to provide customized features to enhance your visit to the website. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Users should consult their browser help files for instructions on how to refuse cookies.
